kutasoftware.com 2019-10-07

# Kuta Software Policies

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how Kuta Software LLC collects, protects, uses, and shares information of visitors of www.kutasoftware.com and users of our desktop software products for teachers: Infinite Pre-Algebra, Infinite Algebra 1, Infinite Geometry, Infinite Algebra 2, Infinite Precalculus, and Infinite Calculus.

The Kuta Works learning management system has its own privacy policy [available here](https://cdn.works.kutasoftware.com/legal/privacy.html).

#### Visitors to www.kutasoftware.com

Our web site may use logging and Google Analytics to track usage trends. Some of the information collected is described below, but please read [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for more details.

  * Google assigned ids
  * Internet protocol addresses
  * Areas of site visited with date and time
  * Operating system and browser settings
  * Referring page
  * Other data to track usage of site

#### Credit Card Transactions

Your personal information is collected in order to process the credit card transaction.

#### Users of Desktop Software

The desktop software for teachers includes Infinite Pre-Algebra, Infinite Algebra 1, Infinite Geometry, Infinite Algebra 2, Infinite Precalculus, and Infinite Calculus.

When desktop software is used for the first time, it must be activated by the teacher or other faculty member. During activation, the following information is collected.

  * Windows or Mac user name of teacher or other faculty member
  * Computer description entered by user
  * Computer id

#### Usage of Personal Information

Personal information is used solely to provide the services to users.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Personal information is never given, sold, rented, or otherwise shared with any other company, group, or person. Personal information will only be shared when legally required to do so, such as when ordered by a court.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Kuta Software LLC may revise and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantive changes by posting a message on the web site.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about Kuta Software LLC or this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
